spacedart.com 2015-02-06

# Privacy Policy| www.spacedart.com

This Privacy policy is subject to the terms of the Site Policy (User agreement) of spacedart. This policy is effective from the date and time a user registers with spacedart by filling up the Registration form and accepting the terms and conditions laid out in the Site Policy.

In order to provide a personalised browsing experience, spacedart may collect personal information from you. Additionally some of our websites may require you to complete a registration form or seek some information from you. When you let us have your preferences, we will be able to deliver or allow you to access the most relevant information that meets your end.

To extend this personalized experience spacedart may track the IP address of a user's computer and save certain information on your system in the form of cookies. A user has the option of accepting or declining the cookies of this website by changing the settings of your browser.

The personal information provided by the users to spacedart will not be provided to third parties without previous consent of the user concerned. Information of a general nature may however be revealed to external parties

Every effort will be made to keep the information provided by users in a safe manner, the information will be displayed on the website will be done so only after obtaining consent from the users. Any user browsing the site generally is not required to disclose his identity or provide any information about him/her, it is only at the time of registration you will be required to furnish the details in the registration form.

A full user always has the option of not providing the information which is not mandatory. You are solely responsible for maintaining confidentiality of the User password and user identification and all activities and transmission performed by the User through his user identification and shall be solely responsible for carrying out any online or off-line transaction involving credit cards / debit cards or such other forms of instruments or documents for making such transactions and SRK Green iPortals Private Limited assumes no responsibility or liability for their improper use of information relating to such usage of credit cards / debit cards used by the subscriber online / off-line.

You agree that SRK Green iPortals Private Limited may use personal information about you to improve its marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve the Site's content and product offerings, and customise the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customised experience while using the Site.

You agree that SRK Green iPortals Private Limited may use your personal information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, we encourage you to opt out of the receipt of certain communications in your profile. You may make changes to your profile at any time. It is the belief of SRK Green iPortals Private Limited that privacy of a person can be best guaranteed by working in conjunction with the Law enforcement authorities.

All SRK Green iPortals Private Limited websites including spacedart fully comply with all Indian Laws applicable. SRK Green iPortals Private Limited has always cooperated with all law enforcement inquires. SRK Green iPortals Private Limited may disclose all or part of your personal details in response to a request from the law enforcement authorities or in a case of bonafide requirement to prevent an imminent breach of the law.

We value the trust you place in spacedart.com. That's why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically. SpaceDart.com is one of the fastest growing Real Estate portal committed to fulfil all your home buying, selling and renting needs. From when you start your search for a Property, Apartment, Flat or villa to when you finalise the deal for your dream home, we are with you; to guide you at every stage of your home buying endeavour.

**Creation of Account**

• To access and use some section on Spacedart.com that is restricted only to registered users, you need to create an account on Spacedart.com.  
• To create an account we need your email address, which could then be used to login to Spacedart.com.  
• You have to accept the terms of service before creating an account on Spacedart.com. Invitation to join Spacedart.com  
• Email addresses to which invitation(s) are sent, are stored in the system for logging purposes.  
• We may use these email addresses to send periodic notifications about the service. Receivers can opt out and will never be sent any email from Spacedart.com 

**Personal Information**

• We ask for some personal information when you create a Spacedart account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access..  
• We take the privacy of our users very seriously.  
• We will never sell, rent, or share your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes.  
• Spacedart will have a right to use the information to provide personalised advertisements and offers, or to include that information in compilations developed by spacedart, or to develop derivative works based on that information.
